MD. FAYZULLAH AMAN

WEB DEVELOPER



CONTACT

- ☑ fayzullahaman@gmail.com
- **\(\)** 01795504043 / 01916955766
- (1) Uttor Badda, Dhaka, Bangladesh
- 🔇 fayzullahaman.bdprogrammers.com
- in linkedin.com/in/fayzullahaman
- github.com/fayzullahaman

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

JavaScript, jQuery

PHP, MySQL

WordPress

Angular

React

CodeIgniter

Larayel

Vue

ABOUT ME

Assalamu Alaikum

Nice to meet you! I have 5 years of experience as computer operator. Recently I completed web development course from IsDB-BISEW and gained experience in web development. Now I am working in web design and development. Languages I know are HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Jquery, PHP, MySQL, WordPress, Angular, React, CodeIgniter, Laravel and Vue. I am very interested in sharing my skills in web development to the public. My passion is creating and developing a professional, beautiful website. I am committed to maintain a professional relationship with my clients and provide efficient and reliable service according to their needs. Contact me now to discuss your next project.

TRAINING

Web Application Development with PHP and Frameworks (WDPF)

Institute: IsDB-BISEW IT Scholarship Program.

Address: E/8-A, Rokeya Sharani, Sher-e-Bangla Nagar. Dhaka-1207,

Bangladesh

Duration: February 2022 – Running

Round: 51

PROJECTS

Restaurant Management

This project developed by React js and Mysql. Where have the full features of a Restaurant Management System.

Employee Management

This project developed by PHP and Mysql.

Real Estate Management

This project developed by React is and CodeIgniter.

REFERENCE

Md. Moshaidul Islam

Project Consultant

IsDB-BISEW IT Scholarship Program.

Address: E/8-A, Rokeya Sharani, Sher-e-Bangla Nagar. Dhaka-1207

Phone: +8801711071219

E-mail: moshaidul@gmail.com

Syed Ziaul Habib

Zend certified Engineer, OCA, MCTS Instructor of The Computer Ltd.

Address: Dhaka Metropolitan Scout Market, 54 Inner Circular Road, Purana Paltan Line, Dhaka-1000

Phone: +8801749752942 E-mail: roobon@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Computer Operator

The Royal Scientific Publications 2018 - 2022

Data Entry Operator

Golden Harvest InfoTech Ltd.

2017 - 2018

Data Entry Operator

Computer Graphics & Design Ltd. 2016 - 2017

2017

EDUCATION

Masters

Al-Hadith & Islamic Studies

Islamic University

2016-2017

HSC / Alim

Humanities

Khamar Bari Nesaria Fazil Madrasah

2012

Honor's

Al-Hadith & Islamic Studies

Islamic University

2012-2016

SSC / Dakhil

Science

Darunnazat Siddikia Kamil Madrasah

2010

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Father's Name : Md. Mofazzal Hossain

Mother's Name : Khadiza Begum Date of Birth : 29/12/1995 National ID No : 3713190928

Permanent Address: Amirabad, Madaripur Sadar, Madaripur.

Present Address: Khanbag Mosjid, Uttar Badda, Dhaka-1212

Marital status : Unmarried Nationality : Bangladeshi